<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv date="2024/01/13" source-info-url="http://www.scbcplayer.com" source-info-name="SCBC Player"><channel id="SCBC Television"><display-name>SCBC Television</display-name><url>http://www.scbcplayer.com</url></channel><programme start="20240113201500 +0100" stop="20240113204400 +0100" channel="SCBC Television"><title lang="en">TED Talk</title><sub-title lang="en">We should all be feminists   Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie</sub-title><desc lang="en">Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie a renowned Nigerian novelist was born in Nigeria in 1977. She grew up in the university town of Nsukka, Enugu State where she attended primary and secondary schools, and briefly studied Medicine and Pharmacy. She then moved to the United States to attend college, graduating summa cum laude from Eastern Connecticut State University with a major in Communication and a minor in Political Science. She holds a Masters degree in Creative Writing from Johns Hopkins and a Masters degree in African Studies from Yale University. She was a 2005-2006 Hodder Fellow at Princeton, where she taught introductory fiction. Chimamanda is the author of Half of a Yellow Sun, which won the 2007 Orange Prize For Fiction; and Purple Hibiscus, which won the 2005 Best First Book Commonwealth Writers' Prize and the 2004 Debut Fiction Hurston/Wright Legacy Award. In 2009, her collection of short stories, The Thing around Your Neck was published. She was named one of the twenty most important fiction writers today under 40 years old by The New Yorker and was recently the guest speaker at the 2012 annual commonwealth lecture. She featured in the April 2012 edition of Time Magazine, celebrated as one of the 100 Most Influential People in the World. She currently divides her time between the United States and Nigeria.</desc></programme><programme start="20240113204400 +0100" stop="20240113224500 +0100" channel="SCBC Television"><title lang="en">Africa Cup of Nations 2023</title><title lang="en">Africa Cup of Nations 2023</title><sub-title lang="en" /><sub-title lang="en" /><desc lang="en" /><desc lang="en" /></programme><programme start="20240113224500 +0100" stop="20240113231500 +0100" channel="SCBC Television"><title lang="en">Real Engineering</title><sub-title lang="en">The Insane Engineering of the 787</sub-title><desc lang="en">The Insane Engineering of the 787.mp4</desc></programme><programme start="20240113231500 +0100" stop="20240114064000 +0100" channel="SCBC Television"><title lang="eng">Music</title><title lang="en">Music</title><sub-title lang="eng">Music</sub-title><sub-title lang="en">Music</sub-title><desc lang="eng">Music</desc><desc lang="en">African Music</desc></programme><programme start="20240114064000 +0100" stop="" channel="SCBC Television"><title lang="en">The Legacy Of Purpose </title><sub-title lang="en">The Legacy Of Purpose - Ep. 04</sub-title><desc lang="en">On this episode of The Legacy of Purpose we feature MEL2017 guest presenter, Ms. Phylicia Fanta. Phylicia tells us a little about herself and what we should expect from her presentation at MEL2017.</desc></programme></tv>